feedify.net 2017-01-24

# Feedify - Privacy

Atizva Technologies (we" or "us") values its visitors' privacy. This privacy policy is for this website Feedify.net and served by Atizva Technologies and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it.

The policy sets out the different areas where user privacy is concerned and outlines the obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owners. Furthermore the way this website processes, stores and protects user data and information will also be detailed within this policy.

## 1\. Information We Collect

  1. Data Received from you: When you use the Services, consult with our customer service team, send us an email, post on our blog, or communicate with us in any way, you’re giving us information that we collect. That information may include your and your Subscribers’ IP address, name, physical address, email address, phone number, credit card information, operating system, as well as details like gender, occupation, location, birth date, purchase history, and other demographic information. By giving us this information, you consent to your information being collected, used, disclosed, transferred to us and stored by us, as described in our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.
  2. List and Email Information: When we receive your customer List or create an email with the Services, we have and may access the data on your list and the information in your email.
  3. Information from your Use of the Service: We may get information about how and when you use the Services, store it in log files associated with your account, and link it to other information we collect about you. This information may include, for example, your IP address, time, date, browser used, and actions you’ve taken within the application.
  4. Web Tracking: When you user our services, we track your Members/customers, we may track behavior such as who opened/clicked on the products. We do that to measure the performance of our products activated by you and to show you the analytics behavior and reports about how your campaign performed and what actions your Subscribers took also it may be used improve our features for specific segments to Members.
  5. Security: We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

## 2\. Other information we collect

We may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as (for example) the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of our Web site(s); research and development; customer- and account administration; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely.

## 3\. Use of Cookies

This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

## 4\. Updates to privacy policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices.. All updates will be posted on this page.

## 5\. Questions & Concerns

If you have any questions or comments, or if you want to update, delete, or change any Personal Information we hold, or you have a concern about the way in which we have handled any privacy matter please use our _contact form_ to get in touch. You may also contact us by postal mail or email at:

Atizva Technologies  
Attn. Privacy Officer  
support@feedify.net  
A-301, Anmol Space,  
Anand Bazaar,  
Indore – 452001  
India
